Guide to the American Planning Association records, 1925-2015.
American Planning Association records,
- APA Governance Committee Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- APA Governance Leadership Letter, 1979-1998 (Box 63, Folder 20-24)
- Governance Leadership Letter, 1979-1998 (Box 64, Folder 1-22)
- Newport, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Denver, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Boise, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Atlanta, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Cincinnati, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- New York, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Milwaukee, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- San Antonio, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Virginia Beach, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- St. Louis, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Montreal, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Tampa, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Minneapolis, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Chicago, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Cincinnati, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Seattle, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Washington D.C., 1982 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Dallas, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Denver, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Boston, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- APA Board of Directors, 1978-1980 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- APA Board, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 23-25)
- APA Board, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 26-29)
- APA Board Minutes, 1930-1932 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1988-1990 (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1985-1998 (Box 66, Folder 5-7)
- Board Minuets and Agendas, 1978-1984 (Box 66, Folder 8-9)
- Leadership Letter, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 10-12)
- Leadership Letter, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 13-17)
- Leadership Letter, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Restructuring, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Governance Report, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Governance Committee Board member profiles, 1983-1984 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- APA/AICP Hiring Executive Director, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Leadership Letter, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Leadership Letter, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Leadership Letter, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Planning Commissioner Task Force Minutes and Correspondence Part 1 of 2, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Planning Commissioner Task Force Minutes and Correspondence Part 2 of 2, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Readex and Final Questionnaire Planning Commission Task Force, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Ethics Awareness Committee, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Planning Commission Task Force - Staff Background Material, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Planning Official Advisory Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Planning Commissioner Task Force Report, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Planning Commissioner Report to Board, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Planning Officials Education Plan Report to Board, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Proposed Council of Planning Officials - Planning Commissioners Task Force, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- 54 Largest Cities, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Big City Planning Directors, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Video of the City, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- International Exchange Program, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Letters From Feds to Michael Barker, Executive Directors, APA, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- APA Board of Directors - New Orleans, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- APA Minutes - Baltimore, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- APA Board Minutes - New Orleans, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- APA National Elections Part 1 of 2, 1982-1985 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- APA National Elections Part 2 of 2, 1982-1985 (Box 67, Folder 20)
- APA Nominating Committee, 1979-1983 (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Transition Old Articles and New, 1985-1990 (Box 67, Folder 23)
- APA, ASPO, AICP Transition Part 1 of 5, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 24)
- APA, ASPO, AICP Transition Part 2 of 5, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 25)
- APA, ASPO, AICP Transition Part 3 of 5, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 26)
- APA, ASPO, AICP Transition Part 4 of 5, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 27)
- APA, ASPO, AICP Transition Part 5 of 5, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 28)
- 1983 Election Results (Box 67, Folder 29)
- Elections 1979, 1980, 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 67, Folder 30)
- Election Flyers 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 31)
- Board Meeting Minutes Part 1 of 2, 1978-1988 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Board Meeting Minutes Part 2 of 2, 1978-1988 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors Conference - San Francisco, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors Policies, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Board of Directors Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Board of Directors - Chicago, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Board of Directors - Chicago, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Board of Directors - Chicago, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Board of Directors - Denver, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Board of Directors - Vancouver, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Board of Directors - Washington, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Board of Directors - San Diego, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Board of Directors - New Orleans, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Board of Directors - Baltimore, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Board of Directors - Kansas City, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Board of Directors - Indianapolis, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Board of Directors - Miami Part 1 of 2, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors - Miami Part 2 of 2, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- APA, AICP National Files Part 1 of 3, 1991-1992 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- APA, AICP National Files Part 2 of 3, 1991-1992 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- APA, AICP National Files Part 3 of 3, 1991-1992 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Conference Programs, 1969-1972 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Conference Programs, 1973-1975, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Conference Program, 1978-1981 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Conference Programs, 1982, 1984, 1986, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Conference Programs, 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Conference Programs, 1991-1993 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Conference Programs, 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Conference Programs, 1997-1999 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Conference Programs, 2000-2002 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Conference Programs, 2003-2004 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Conference Programs, 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Conference Programs, 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Conference Programs, 2009-2010 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Update on Impact Fees, Extractions, Takings Law, and Legilsation, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Update on Constitutional Law, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 20)
- Understanding the Private Market and Negotiating with Developers, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Understanding Design Context, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 22)
- Transportation Management and Edge Cities, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 23)
- Transportation in the Community, Metropolitan, Regional and State Plans, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 24)
- Training Made Easy, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 25)
- Time Management and Personal Plans, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 26)
- Suburban Open Space Planning and Design, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 27)
- The Rubber and the Road: Infrastructure Capacity Planning, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 28)
- Zoning Enforcement Techniques, Romero Crandall, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Writing Well, Sylvia Lewis, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Regulations and Affordable Housing, Edith M. Netter, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Protecting Wildlife and Open Space, Kent S. Butler, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Primer on Constitutional Issues, Edward Ziegler, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Planning for Community Character, Gary Pivo, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Planning by Consensus in Downtown Revitalization, Michael Black, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- CD Roms Bookstore Product, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Packaged Workshops, Undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Planning Board Membership, Undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Education Catalog, 2001-2002 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- AICP Exam Prep Course, 1999-2003 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Audio/Web Conference, 1998-2007 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- High School Essay Contest, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- ISTEA: Public Involvement and Major Investment Analysis, 1993-1994 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Integrating Environmental and Traditioanl Land-Use Planning, Michael McCormick, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Gambling with History/Future, Gregory, Chadbourne, Walker, Eadington, Meyer-Arendt, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Forecasting and Evaluation for Transportation Planning, James R. Gosnell, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Environmental Regulations, James Berry, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Developing and Streamliinging Zoning Administration, George N. Arimes, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Innovative State Plannign and Regional Approaches, Berry, Merriam, Salkin, Ziegler, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Planners Role in Superfund, William Lamont, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Performance Zoning, Phillip B. Herr, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Performance Zoning, Gordon Herr, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 24)
- New Statutes to Bolster Local and Regional Plans and Regulations, Patricia Slakin, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 25)
- Linking Economic Development and Planning, Barbara Cole, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 26)
- Land-Use Lawsuits, Dwight Merriam, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 27)
- Land Use and the Constitution, Blaesser, Weinstein, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 28)
- Design Implementation, Winter, Costello, and Race, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 29)
- Conflict Resolution and Strategic Analysis, Jerome L. Kaufman, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 30)
- Community Planning and Big Box Retailing, Beaumont, Smith, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 31)
- Community Decision-making in Urban Design, Bruce Race, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 32)
- Collaborative Planning, DuPraw, Potaapchuk, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 33)
- City Beautiful: Zoning for Aesthetics, Chris Duerkson, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 34)
- Building Vision and Action, Philip B. Herr, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 35)
- Building a Top-Notch Planning Agency, Ernest L. Freeman, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 36)
- Avoiding or Winning the Land Use Lawsuit, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 37)
- Pre-1992 Video Materials, Undated (Box 70, Folder 38)
- Alabama, 1996-2002 (Box 70, Folder 39-40)
- Alaska, 1997-2004 (Box 70, Folder 41)
- Arizona, 1997-2001 (Box 70, Folder 42-43)
- Arkansas, 1997-2002 (Box 70, Folder 44)
- California, 1996-2002 (Box 70, Folder 45-46)
- Colorado, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 47)
- Connecticut, 1998-2002 (Box 70, Folder 48)
- Delaware, 1997-1999 (Box 70, Folder 49)
- Florida, 2000-2002 (Box 70, Folder 50-51)
- Florida, 1995-2000 (Box 71, Folder 1-5)
- Georgia, 1996-2002 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Hawaii, 1997-2002 (Box 71, Folder 7-9)
- National Capital, 1997-2002 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Nebraska, 1997-2002 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Nevada, 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- New Jersey, 1997-2001 (Box 71, Folder 13-14)
- New Mexico, 1997-2002 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- New York Metro, 1997-2001 (Box 71, Folder 16-19)
- New York Upstate, 1995-2001 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- North Carolina, 1999-2001 (Box 71, Folder 21-25)
- Planning News
  - Illinois Planning News, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Planning News, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Indiana Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Indiana Planning News, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Iowa Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Kansas Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Kansas Planning News, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Kentucky Planning News, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Ohio Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Louisiana Planning News, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Maryland Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Maryland Planning News, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Planning News, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Planning News, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts Planning News, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Michigan Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Michigan Planning News, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Michigan Planning News, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Minnesota Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Minnesota Planning News, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Minnesota Planning News, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Minnesota Planning News, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Mississippi Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Missouri Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Northern New England Planning News, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Northern New England Planning News, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Kentucky Planning News, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Ohio Planning News, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Ohio Planning News, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Oklahoma Planning News, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Oregon Planning News, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Oregon Planning News, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Oregon Planning News, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Oregon Planning News, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Planning News, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Planning News, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Planning News, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania Planning News, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Rhode Island Planning News, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - South Carolina Planning News, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - South Carolina Planning News, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - South Carolina Planning News, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Tennessee Planning News, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Texas Planning News, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Texas Planning News 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Texas Planning News 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Utah Planning News, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Utah Planning News, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Utah Planning News, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Planning News, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Planning News, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Planning News, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Planning News, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Washington State Planning News, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Washington State Planning News, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - West Virginia Planning News, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - West Central Planning News, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Wisconsin Planning News, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Wisconsin Planning News, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- APA 2001 Planning Conference Roster, New Orleans, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Summaries of State Case Planning Law, Part 1 of 8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Summaries of State Case Planning Law, part 2 of 8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Summaries of State Case Planning Law, Part 3 of 8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Summaries of State Case Planning Law, Part 4 of 8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Summaries of State Case Planning Law, Part 5 of 8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Summaries of State Case Planning Law, Part 6 of 8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Summaries of State Case Planning Law, Part 7 of 8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Summaries of State Case Planning Law, Part 8 of 8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Revolutionary Ideas In Planning: Proceedings of the 1998 National Planning Conference (Book) (Box 74, Folder 14)
- APA National Planning Conference: Contrasts and Transitions (Book), 1997 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- AICP Examination Preparation Course, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- The National AICP Examination Course Guidebook, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Manager's Planning Guide and Improving the Development Review System, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- The Best of Contemporary Community Planning, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Readership Survey Among Subscribers of the Journal of the American Planning Association, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- New Product Survey, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Accessory Dwelling Units, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Planning Communities for the 21sst Century, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- The Joint Reference Library, A Memoir, by Lucile Keck, 1932-1963 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Marketing Segmentation Review,Analysis and Recommendations, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Membership Directory, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Planning Advisory Service, 1960-1990 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- A Marketing Needs and Structural Review and Analysis, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- APA Market Survey, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- APA-ASAE Peer Review Report, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Comments on APA-AICP Membership Surveys, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- American Institute of Certified Planners (AICP) Survey Findsings, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- APA Surveys of Planning Officials and Planning Directors, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 18)
- APA-AICP- Professional Planner Member Survey, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 19)
- AICP - Planning Consultant Practice Survey, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Commendation Honoring the APA, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- APA Interact and Annual Reports, 1998-2007 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- City Parks Forum, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Mountains and Shores, 2004 (Box 75, Folder 24)
- Growing Smart Newsletter, 1995-2000 (Box 75, Folder 25)
- Growing Smart Minutes, 1995-1998 (Box 75, Folder 26)
- Planning for Smart Growth, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 27)
- APA: Land Use Law Series - "Innovative State Planning and Regional Approaches" 1 of 2, Undated; V-5620 (Box 76)
- APA: Land Use Law Series - "Innovative State Planning and Regional Approaches" 2 of 2, Undated; V-5621 (Box 76)
- APA: Small Town and Rural Planning Series - "Linking Economic Development and Planning" 1 of 1, Undated; V-5622 (Box 76)
- APA: Transportation Planning for the 1990's Series - "ISTEA: Public Involvement and Major Investment Analysis" 1 of 1, Undated; V-5623 (Box 76)
- APA: Land Use Law Series - "Land-Use Lawsuits" 1 of 2, Undated; V-5624 (Box 76)
- APA: Land Use Law Series - "Land-Use Lawsuits" 2 of 2, Undated; V-5625 (Box 76)
- APA: Guiding Urban Design Series - "Design Implementation" 1 of 2, Undated; V-5626 (Box 76)
- APA: Guiding Urban Design Series - "Design Implementation" 2 of 2, Undated; V-5627 (Box 76)
- APA: Innovative State Planning and Regional Approaches - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5628 (Box 76)
- APA: Innovative State Planning and Regional Approaches - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5629 (Box 76)
- APA: Linking Economic Development and Planning - 1 of 1, Undated; V-5630 (Box 76)
- A Mock Commission Hearing, Undated; V-5631 (Box 76)
- APA: Integrating Enviornmental and Traditional Land-Use Planning - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5632 (Box 76)
- APA: Integrating Environmental and Traditional Land-Use Planning - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5633 (Box 76)
- APA: Innovative State Planning and Regional Approaches - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5634 (Box 76)
- APA: Innovative State Planning and Regional Approaches - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5635 (Box 76)
- APA: Land Use Lawsuits - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5636 (Box 76)
- APA: Land Use Lawsuits - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5637 (Box 76)
- APA: Environmental Regulations - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5638 (Box 76)
- APA: Environmental Regulations - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5639 (Box 76)
- AICP Video Education: Gambling With History, Undated; V-5640 (Box 76)
- AICP Video Education: Gambling With The Future, Undated; V-5641 (Box 76)
- APA: Mock Hearing, Undated; V-5642 (Box 76)
- Video: Update on Impact Fees Part 1 of 2, Undated; V-5564 (Box 77)
- Video: Update on Impact Fees Part 2 of 2, Undated; V-5565 (Box 77)
- Video: Meeting Management Part 1 of 2, Undated; V-5566 (Box 77)
- Video: Meeting Management Part 2 of 2, Undated; V-5567 (Box 77)
- Video: Historic Preservation, Undated; V-5568 (Box 77)
- Video: Training Made Easy Copy 1 of 3, Undated; V-5569 (Box 77)
- Video: Training Made Easy Copy 2 of 3, Undated; V-5569 (Box 77)
- Video: Training Made Easy Copy 3 of 3, Undated; V-5569 (Box 77)
- Video: Update on Constitutional Law Copy 1 of 3, Undated; V-5570 (Box 77)
- Video: Update on Constitutional Law Copy 2 of 3, Undated; V-5570 (Box 77)
- Video: Update on Constitutional Law Copy 3 of 3, Undated; V-5570 (Box 77)
- Video: Ethics Part 1 of 5, Undated; V-5571 (Box 77)
- Video: Ethics Part 2 of 5, Undated; V-5572 (Box 77)
- Video: Ethics Part 3 of 5, Undated; V-5573 (Box 77)
- Video: Ethics Part 4 of 5, Undated; V-5574 (Box 77)
- Video: Ethics Part 5 of 5, Undated; V-5575 (Box 77)
- Video: Why Plan? Copy 1 of 4, Undated; V-5576 (Box 77)
- Video: Why Plan? Copy 2 of 4, Undated; V-5576 (Box 77)
- Video: Why Plan? Copy 3 of 4, Undated; V-5576 (Box 77)
- Video: Why Plan? Copy 4 of 4, Undated; V-5576 (Box 77)
- Video: Transportation Mangement Copy 1 of 2, Undated; V-5577 (Box 77)
- Video: Transportation Management Copy 2 of 2, Undated; V-5577 (Box 77)
- Video: AICP/Issues in Environmental Law, Undated; V-5578 (Box 77)
- Video: Transportation In The Community Part 1 of 2, Undated; V-5579 (Box 77)
- Video: Transportation In The Community Part 2 of 2, Undated; V-5580 (Box 77)
- Video: Trainers Tips, Undated; V-5581 (Box 77)
- Video: The Planning Director Series, Undated; V-5582 (Box 77)
- Video: City Beautiful, Undated; V-5582 (Box 77)
- Video: Guiding Urban Design, Undated; V-5583 (Box 77)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 1 of 12, 2003; V-5584 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 2 of 12, 2003; V-5585 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 3 of 12, 2003; V-5586 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 4 of 12, 2003; V-5587 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 5 of 12, 2003; V-5588 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 6 of 12, 2003; V-5589 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 7 of 12, 2003; V-5590 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 8 of 12, 2003; V-5591 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 9 of 12, 2003; V-5592 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 10 of 12, 2003; V-5593 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 11 of 12, 2003; V-5594 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 12 of 12, 2003; V-5595 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Atlanta, Cassettes ? Part 1 of 1, 1989; V-5596 (Box 78)
- Video: APA Update on Impact Fees, Exactions, Takings Law and Legislation, Part 1 of 2, Undated; V-5597 (Box 78)
- Video: APA Update on Impact Fees, Exactions, Takings Law and Legislation, Part 2 of 2, Undated; V-5598 (Box 78)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 1 of 9, 2003; V-5599 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 2 of 9, 2003; V-5600 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 3 of 9, 2003; V-5601 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 4 of 9, 2003; V-5602 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 5 of 9, 2003; V-5603 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 6 of 9, 2003; V-5604 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 7 of 9, 2003; V-5605 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 8 of 9, 2003; V-5606 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Denver, Cassettes ? Part 9 of 9, 2003; V-5607 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Chicago, Cassettes ? Part 1 of 5, 2002; V-5608 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Chicago, Cassettes ? Part 2 of 5, 2002; V-5609 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Chicago, Cassettes ? Part 3 of 5, 2002; V-5610 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Chicago, Cassettes ? Part 4 of 5, 2002; V-5611 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, Chicago, Cassettes ? Part 5 of 5, 2002; V-5612 (Box 79)
- APA National Planning Conference, San Diego, Cassettes ? Part 1 of 1, 1997; V-5613 (Box 80)
- APA National Planning Conference, Toronto, Cassettes ? Part 1 of 6, 1995; V-5614 (Box 80)
- APA National Planning Conference, Toronto, Cassettes ? Part 2 of 6, 1995; V-5615 (Box 80)
- APA National Planning Conference, Toronto, Cassettes ? Part 3 of 6, V-5616 (Box 80)
- APA National Planning Conference, Toronto, Cassettes ? Part 4 of 6, 1995; V-5617 (Box 80)
- APA National Planning Conference, Toronto, Cassettes ? Part 5 of 6, 1995; V-5618 (Box 80)
- APA National Planning Conference, Toronto, Cassettes ? Part 6 of 6, 1995; V-5619 (Box 80)
- APA: Land Use Law Series - "Primer on Constitutional Issues" - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5643 (Box 85)
- APA: Land Use Law Series - "Primer on Constitutional Issues" - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5644 (Box 85)